pdfcomplete.com 2012-05-21

# PDF Complete Home

---  
  
The following statement discloses the PDF Complete Inc ("PDFC") consumer privacy practices for the PDF Complete Web Site ("Site") and software sold and/or supported ("Software") on this Site. We do update our policy from time to time without notice so please check back periodically. All updates will be published at this Site. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Site or Software, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Personal Information

PDF Complete understands your desire to protect personal information. We intend to inform you how your personal information will be gathered, tracked or used, and to give you choices. If choices are not offered on web pages where your personal information is obtained, please select one of the communication channels at the bottom of this statement to indicate your communication preferences.

General Information we gather and track

We request personal information when you place an order, activate or register a product, request a service, answer a survey, enter a contest, correspond with us or engage in certain other activities on our website. For example, If you submit an order on-line with us, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction such as your name, address, and credit card number. If you request technical support online, we will ask you for information necessary to complete the transaction such as your name address and information about your computer hardware, software and the nature of the problem you are experiencing. You make the decision whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the transaction.

How we use the General Information we gather and track

We use personally identifiable information in the following ways:

  * To provide you with information about product upgrades, new products, services, newsletters, informative emails, and research on future product ideas or improvements;
  * To assist us in creating content that is relevant to you;
  * To provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you;
  * To assist us in creating better products and services to meet your needs;
  * To allow you to purchase, download, and manage product licenses, obtain access to services or otherwise engage in activities you select;
  * To help you quickly find software, services or product information important to you.   

With whom we may share your information

PDFC collects and uses your personal information to operate the Site and deliver the software and services that you have requested. PDFC also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from PDFC and its affiliates. PDFC may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. PDFC may provide your personally indentifiable information to the affiliate that initially referred you to the Site.

PDFC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. PDFC may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In addition, PDF Complete may retain the services of outside contractors to provide services for us. They may be used to ship products, provide technical support, or handle order processing. We require that these contractors keep the personal information of customers secure and confidential. We also require that these contractors use personal information only on behalf of PDF Complete. PDFC will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on PDFC; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of PDFC; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of PDFC, or the public.

Opt out of providing certain information

PDF Complete provides a number of ways for you to opt out of receiving additional information from us or having us provide your personal information to our partners. We may offer you these choices at the time you give us your information. If you are on a PDF Complete web page that requires personal information but does not offer communication choices, or would like to change your preferences for information that you have previously provided, please use one of the communication channels at the bottom of this statement. If you are registering a version of a product that does not provide you the capability to indicate your communication preferences, please use one of the communication channels at the bottom of this statement. If you do not wish to continue receiving our email newsletters or bulletins you can opt out of receiving these communications by replying to the unsubscribe in the subject line in the email.

Privacy of Children

PDF Complete is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in the online activities and interests of their children. PDF Complete does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and PDF Complete does not target its websites to children under 13.

Software Updates and Activations Provided Online

PDF Complete provides a online update service to provide improved versions our software. These updates are provided to correct operational defects and provide additional feature functionality to our users. As part of the software update process, we collect the following information: a statistically unique number (but not a Windows GUID), your serial number, your IP address, software version, type of operating system, the number of pages and documents that have been created, the number of users, installation language, and the number of days used.  PDF Complete provides a online activation service to provide full function versions our software. As part of the software activation process, we collect the following additional information: serial number, valid email address, name, company name, and country name and you may optionally specify address and telephone contact information. We collect this information in order to help us better understand the usage patterns of our products to provide more timely and relevent updates. We also use this information for planning and forecasting server loads, upgrade patterns, licensing, and purchasing patterns. The information is also used to generate aggregate statistics about how our software, web site, and update services are used so that we may provide the best possible support to our customers.

Security

We have taken security measures, consistent with international information practices, to protect your personal information. These measures include technical and procedural steps to protect your data from misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, loss, alteration, or destruction. Credit card information is transmitted using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption.  
Since PDF Complete is a global company, we provide company information to our worldwide offices. The personal information that you have provided to us may be transferred to other PDF Complete offices around the world. Also, in certain countries our outside contractors might undertake the collection, transferring, storage and processing of your information.  
We make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to update or correct your personal information. If you believe that PDF Complete does not have your current personal information, you can update it by using one of the communication channels at the bottom of this statement.

Use of Cookies

The PDFC Site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time or qualify you for special offers that PDFC may make available from time to time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. Cookies simplify the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same PDFC Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the PDFC features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the PDFC Site that you visit.

Business Partner and Cobranded Web Sites

At the PDF Complete Site, there are a number of links to companies with whom we have a relationship. PDF Complete is not responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners. We encourage you to read their privacy statements, as they may differ from ours. We also link to cobranded web sites that are maintained by PDF Complete and one or more of our business partners. When you submit information to one of our cobranded sites you may be submitting it to both PDF Complete and our business partners and the privacy policies of these cobranded sites may differ from this privacy policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policies on any cobranded site to which you link for information on the privacy practices of that site. 

Customer Support and Discussion Information

Please remember that information you submit in a for purposes of customer or product support in a discussion group or forum will be deemed public information and is not confidential. There is a risk in such communication venues that information can be collected and used by others. Please be careful and responsible when you are online. 

Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, comments, or would like to change your communication preferences, please contact us using one of the options below:

[Email your Privacy comments or questions to privacy@pdfcomplete.com](mailto:privacy@pdfcomplete.comSubject=Request)

|
